梅达把她的手指...
Mayda slides her fingers in...
一直伸进她的婚戒里
all the way up to her... her wedding ring.
她把你推倒  然后倾下身来
She pushes you onto your back and leans down.
把手指伸入你的嘴里  让你尝到
Puts the fingers into your mouth so you can... taste them.
戒指的金味儿
The gold of the ring...
你的舌尖可以尝到金属的腥味儿
You could taste the sting of the metal on your tongue...
混合着她的屄味儿
mixed with the taste of her cunt.
她倾下身来  冲你的耳朵低语
She leans down, whispers in your ear,
"我爱你  加吉克
"I love you, Gagik.
我爱你"
I love you."
-我就要来了  -她跨着你  把你拉进体内
- I'm close, man. - She straddles you, pulls you inside...
她的臀部前后摩挲  来回摩擦
grinds her hips back and forth, back and forth--
该死  你真会说
Ah, damn, you're good with words.
"...新罕布什尔两百年来
"...New Hampshire for over 200 years.
一直有些起起落落
There've been ups and downs along the way.
就像大埃默斯基格"
Like the big A-mos-ke-ag."
埃默  埃默斯
Am... Amos--
联系到她了吗
Do you have her?
她不肯接电话
She won't get on the phone.
-那就打给她的保安  -我打了
- Then get her detail on the phone. - I did.
他们不能逼她跟您说话  先生
They can't force her to talk to you, sir.
我们得考虑我单独出席活动  她不在身边时
We need to think about what to say when I show up at this event
该说什么
and she's not with me.
我不想读错词  让情况更糟
And I don't want to make it worse by mispronouncing this.
这个词怎么读
How do you say this word?
他们怎么不给讲话注音
They didn't put in the goddamn phonetics in this speech!
又不能让我自己去查
And I can't be expected to look this shit up myself!
我替您查  先生
I'll find out for you, sir.
当然  这些年来...
And of course, there's been...
"一直有起起落落"
"...ups and downs along the way."
就像20年代为薪酬和工时而举行的
Like the big Amoskeag strike in the 1920s
大埃默斯基格罢工
over pay and hours.
但这个行业也还是挺过来了
But this industry survived that as well.
这间屋子里的每个人都在传承一个传统
And all of you in this room have been carrying on a tradition
始于国家创始之初的传统
that goes back to the beginning of this country,
你们应该为此感到万分骄傲
and that's something you have to be very, very proud of!
"但这个州还有一项传统
"But there's another tradition in this state:
不自由毋宁死
Live Free or Die.
我妻子..."
Now, my wife--"
这个州还有一项传统
There's another tradition in this state:
不自由毋宁死
Live Free or Die.
当然  你们中一些人可能在报纸上读到了
Now, of course, as some of you may read in the papers,
也听到电视上的权威人士说了
and, uh, hear from the television pundits
我的对手在新罕布什尔有10个百分点的领先
that my opponent has a ten-point lead here in New Hampshire.
但是
But...
你们不能让民调和权威人士指挥你们
you're not gonna let polls and pundits tell you what to do.
-不  -或是告诉你们选举日该怎么投票
- No! - Or tell you how to vote on Election Day.
你们要让他们知道新罕布什尔人民能自己做主
You are gonna show them that New Hampshire makes up its own mind.
桶匠行业欢迎安德伍德总统
谢谢  谢谢大家今天前来
Thank you! Thank you all for coming out today.
天佑美国  谢谢
And God bless America. Thank you.
安德伍德  安德伍德
Underwood! Underwood! Underwood!
谢谢  非常感谢  谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢大家  非常感谢
Thank you all. Thank you all very much.
谢谢
Thank you.
她10分钟前在达拉斯降落了
She landed in Dallas ten minutes ago.
我们的说法是她去为初选打基础了
Our story is she's down there laying groundwork for the primary.
这只能给我们一两天时间
That only gives us a day or two.
如果她不参加活动  他们会觉得我有所隐瞒
If she's not doing events, they'll think we're hiding something.
你觉得她会待在农场吗
You think she'll stay put on the ranch?
我不知道  你盯住她一切活动
I have no idea. You keep track of all of her movements.
访客  是谁  次数
Visitors, names, times,
他们拉的屎什么颜色  臭不臭
the color of their shit and how much it stinks.
-是  先生  -你这就上飞机
- Yes, sir. - And I want you on a plane.
-回华盛顿吗  -去德克萨斯州
- Back to Washington? - Down to Texas.
-她在哪  -主卧
- Where is she? - The master bedroom.
黑尔太太提到她可能要打个盹
Mrs. Hale mentioned that she might take a nap.
我的房间布置好了吗
Is my room made up?
正在掸尘
It's being dusted right now.
-我想看看  -是  女士
- I'd like to take a look. - Yes, ma'am.
德州很重要
Well, Texas is an important state.
获得提名我们需要10%的代表
Nearly 10% of the delegates we need for the nomination.
但您说第一夫人今天会陪您一起来的
But you said the First Lady would be here with you today.
是啊  今早我们考虑了一下
Yes, well, when we assessed things this morning,
对新罕布什尔很有信心
we felt good about New Hampshire.
看看这群人  看他们多热情
I mean, look at this crowd, the enthusiasm.
你好  你好  我的老天
Hello, hello. Oh, my goodness.
你好  你真是可爱  叫什么名字
Hello there, aren't you a cutie? What's your name?
-盖比  -你好  盖比
- Gabby. - Hello, Gabby.
总之  我们想计划未来
Anyway, we wanted to start looking ahead.
克莱尔就是德州人
Claire's from Texas,
所以她提前过去也是应该的
so it made sense for her to head down there early.
你好  你好  谢谢你们前来
Hello. Hello. Thank you for coming out.
你不告诉我情况我就没法做工作
I can't do my job if you keep me in the dark.
你只需要知道你要往声明里写的内容
All you need to know is what you put out in the statement.
-是吵架了吗  -赛斯
- Was it an argument? - Seth.
听着  我每天忙着竞选的各种事
Look, I'm working 20 hours a day here on a normal day
就要干20个小时了  现在还要应付这个
with the campaign in full swing, and now this is on my plate?
我可以控制损害
Look, I can do damage control,
但我得知道损害是什么
but I have to know what the damage is.
好吧  我告诉你  我先去我房间
Okay. I'll fill you in. Let me get up to my room.
欢迎来达拉斯
Welcome to Dallas.
或许是个诱饵
Or maybe it's a decoy,
想骗我们在德州买广告
trying to lure us into making ad-buys in Texas.
那就能解释这为什么没写进她的日程了
That would explain why it wasn't part of her schedule.
你跟我们在达拉斯的朋友通过话了吗
Have you spoken to our friends in Dallas?
没见人  没打电话
No meetings or calls.
如果她有活动  我们会知道的
If she were making the rounds, we'd know.
他们要么是很会掩盖
Well, they're either excellent at covering their tracks,
要么就是出事了
or something's up.
-什么事  -不知道  但我想知道
- Like what? - I don't know, but I wanna find out.
梅达
她要离开我  她怀着我的孩子呢
She's gonna fucking leave me. My kid in her belly.
她却要假装我根本不存在
And she gonna act like I never existed.
大概都把婚戒给当掉了
Probably pawned the wedding ring already.
-多少了  -还差两个
- How many is that? - Two more.
-你能怪她吗  -能  我能
- Can you blame her, though? - Yeah, I can blame her.
我给了她一切  她要夺走我的孩子
I gave her everything. She gonna rob me of my kid?
他上高中时  你还出不去呢
He's gonna be in high school before you're out.
那我也还是他父亲
I'll still be his fucking father.
你得让他们向前看
You gotta let them move on, man.
-否则不公平  -我告诉你什么不公平
- It's unfair not to. - Let me tell you about unfair.
好吗  我进来就不公平
Okay? Unfair is I'm even in here,
那贱婊子都不知道
and that fucking bitch doesn't even know it.
她以为我活该进来
She thinks I belong in this shithole?
你杀了人啊
You did kill a guy.
-你是说你没杀吗  -我没那么说
- Are you saying you didn't? - I didn't say shit.
因为我
Because I...
我有过怀疑
I had my doubts.
什么意思
What do you mean your doubts?
就是
Just...
从没觉得你是个杀人犯  仅此而已
never struck me as a killer, that's all.
你不了解我
You don't know what I am!
拜托
Come on!
放开  我无法呼吸了
Let up! I can't breathe.
我只是说
All I'm saying is...
我做犯罪新闻的时候
I interviewed a lot of murder suspects
采访过很多杀人嫌犯
when I was on the crime beat.
我觉得你是无辜的
I think you're innocent.
我觉得你没杀人
I think you didn't do it.
那些人  他们会活剥了你
These guys, they'll skin you alive.
还逼着你对着镜子看着他们那么做
Make you watch in a mirror while they do it.
什么人
What guys?
听说过洛杉矶的亚美尼亚帮吗
You ever hear of Armenian Power in LA?
-没有  -他们的头号人物
- No. - Their top guy.
那混蛋肯定不会进监狱啊
No way that motherfucker was going to jail, huh?
我没有选择
I didn't have a choice.
那么你没做喽
So, you didn't do it?
我做了什么没做什么无所谓
It doesn't matter what I did or what I didn't do.
重要的是我说我做了什么
It matters what I said I did.
你是为谁背锅
Who did you take the fall for?
《华尔街电讯报》的一项全国民调显示
A national Wall Street Telegraph poll finds
康威州长在共和党竞选中处于领先
Governor Conway leading the Republican field
48%的共和党初选选民表示他是他们的首选
with 48% of GOP primary voters saying he's their first choice,
超过其他候选人20%
over 20% more than any other candidate.
康威自2015年5月
Conway has had a dramatic ascent
康威领跑
宣布参选后支持率就扶摇直上
since he announced his candidacy in May of 2015.
当时《华尔街电讯报》的另一项民调显示
In another Wall Street Telegraph poll conducted at the time,
他只俘获了18%的共和党初选选民
he only captured 18% of GOP primary voters.
很多人认为他的年轻和缺乏...
Many felt that his young age and his lack of...
密查姆
Meechum!
-是  先生  -克莱尔的衣服也在这里
- Yes, sir? - Claire's clothes are here.
我去叫先遣的人
I'll get Advance.
以及他竞选对
Along with his campaign's focus
他成功的纽约州州长任期的强调
on his successful tenure as Governor of New York,
他的服役记录...
his service in the Air...
抱歉  先生
My apologies, sir.
她的衣服是昨晚运来的  我们忘记做调整了
Her wardrobe shipped last night and we neglected to adjust.
-好吧  拿出去就是了  -是  先生
- All right, just get it out. - Yes, sir.
他在爱荷华州的每场活动
Hundreds of supporters lined up
都有上百名支持者排队等候
at nearly every one of his Iowa events,
有时甚至是上千人
sometimes numbering in the thousands.
人群里格外突出的是退伍军人
Prominent in the crowd were military veterans.
康威的祖父是海军一级准将
Conway's grandfather was a Navy chief warrant officer
曾在二战中在太平洋战场作战
who fought in the Pacific theater of World War II.
-康威的表现被与...  -密查姆
- Conway's approach has been likened... - Meechum.
1960年的约翰·F·肯尼迪总统竞选相提并论
...to that of John F. Kennedy's 1960 presidential campaign.
既有公共场合的魅力  又有私下里的从容
A combination of public charm and personal poise.
上周  在一个竞选活动上...
Last week, at a campaign event...
今早你去她房间里时
This morning when you went into her room...
我告诉她我们就要出发了
Uh, I told her we were leaving soon.
她...
She just...
她在看一张照片
She was looking at a photograph...
是您给她的那个曼荼罗
of the mandala, the one you gave her.
...曼彻斯特的活动  但第一夫人不在身侧
...event in Manchester, but without the First Lady.
-安德伍德政府的声明  -晚安  先生
- Reports from the Underwood administration... - Good night, sir.
表示克莱尔·安德伍德
- ...have stated that Claire Underwood...
-陪我一会儿  -先生
- Keep me company for a bit. - Sir?
坐吧  我得看会儿东西
You just have a seat. I've got some reading that I have to do.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
但您说第一夫人今天会陪您一起来的
But you said the First Lady would be here with you today.
是啊  今早我们考虑了一下
Yes, well, when we assessed things this morning,
对新罕布什尔很有信心
we felt good about New Hampshire.
看看这群人  看他们多热情
I mean, look at this crowd, the enthusiasm.
你好  你好  我的老天
Hello, hello. Oh, my goodness.
你好  你真是可爱  叫什么名字
Hello there, aren't you a cutie? What's your name?
-盖比  -你好  盖比
- Gabby. - Hello, Gabby.
把那关掉
Turn that off.
克莱尔就是德州人
Claire's from Texas,
所以她提前过去也是应该的
so it made sense for her to head down there early.
你好  你好  谢谢你们前来
Hello. Hello. Thank you for coming out.
"你真是可爱"
"Hmm, aren't you a cutie?"
-你干什么  -您睡着了  先生
- What are you doing? - You fell asleep, sir.
您的眼镜  我...
Your glasses, I was...
对不起  先生  我不是有意...
I'm sorry, sir. I didn't mean to...
-您没事吧  先生  -有事
- You all right, sir? - No.
我是说  没事  我就是...
I mean, yes. I'm just...
-您需要点什么吗  水  -不用
- Can I get you anything? Some water? - I'm fine.
很晚了  你该睡会儿了
It's late. You should get some sleep.
如果您需要我就留下
I'll stay if you like.
我想一个人待着  不过谢谢你了
I think I'd like to be alone, but thank you.
好的  先生
Of course, sir.
请小心脚下
Watch your step, please.
-莉安  -安德伍德夫人
- LeAnn. - Mrs. Underwood.
-我们去散个步吧  -好
- Let's take a walk. - Of course.
你让一个红[共和党]州又关心起了民主党
You've made the Democrats relevant again in a very red state.
你要我为德州的活动助势吗
You want me to help ramp up the Texas operation?
不  我不是为初选而来的
No, I'm not here for the primary.
我想竞选30选区议员
I'm here to run for the 30th,
我希望你做我的竞选经理
and I want you to run my campaign.
白宫说你是来...
The White House is saying that you're here to--
那只是为了不让国会竞选吸引太多注意
That's just so we don't draw attention to the congressional race.
桃瑞丝·琼斯  她女儿要竞选
Doris Jones, her daughter's running.
得说服那位女议员
The congresswoman would need to be convinced.
你是说西莉娅会退出
You're saying Celia bows out?
她等  两年后  席位就是她的
She waits. In two years, the seat is hers.
至多四年
Four at the most.
-参议员吗  -或许
- Senate? - Possibly.
或者州长  2020年
Or governor, 2020.
总统也同意吗
And the president's on board with this?
完全同意
Completely.
听着  就算你能说服西莉娅
Look, even if you could convince Celia,
那也还有个大问题
there's still a big problem.
-我是白人  -白得彻头彻尾
- That I'm white. - Lily white.
穿着设计师鞋  量体剪裁的衣服
In your designer heels and tailored dresses, I mean...
看看这片地产  安德伍德夫人
look at this property, Mrs. Underwood.
一个跟金博士一起游行的女人
A woman who marched with Dr. King
不会有耐心应付一个...
is not gonna have much patience for...
什么
For what?
外人
An outsider.
我认为我们可以改变她对我的看法
Well, I believe we can change her opinion of me.
听着  我不介意做困难大的事
Look, I don't mind betting against the odds.
否则  我也不会在德州为民主党做顾问了
If I did, I wouldn't be consulting for Democrats in Texas.
-但你所要求的  -你创办你公司时  莉安
- But what you're asking me-- - When you started your firm, LeAnn,
你父亲跟我父亲说你是在犯下大错误
your father told mine that you were making a huge mistake.
那是因为他是个共和党人
That's because he was a Republican.
是啊  但你没有犯错  不是吗
Yes, but you didn't make a mistake, did you?
你证明他错了
You proved him wrong.
很多顾问都能告诉我这为什么不行
Now, a dozen consultants can tell me why this won't work,
但我觉得你能告诉我这为什么行
but I think you can tell me why it can.
密查姆说她进去了一小时
Meechum said she was in there for over an hour.
哈维不是我们的人
We don't own Harvey.
沃恩认为她在等邓巴
Vaughn thinks she's been holding out for Dunbar.
她不会是为初选跟她见面
She wouldn't be meeting with her about the primary.
或许她觉得她可以竞选什么
Maybe she thinks she can run for something.
-什么  这轮吗  -她一直希望当选公职
- What? This cycle? - Elected office has always been her goal.
现在没有缺职
There aren't any open races.
在德州没有  只有桃瑞丝·琼斯
Not in Texas. Except for Doris Jones.
嗯  但她女儿打算竞选那个职位
Yeah, but her daughter's running for that seat.
她还没宣布呢
She hasn't announced yet.
这就给了克莱尔机会
Which gives Claire an opening.
有人吗
Hello?
-有人吗  -莉安
- Hello? - LeAnn?
道格·斯坦普
Doug Stamper.
我还以为我走错了...
Wasn't sure if I was in the right--
德州就这么打招呼吗
Is that how you say hi in Texas?
抱歉  电梯周末一般是停用的
Sorry, the elevators are usually locked down on the weekends.
我们楼里进过盗窃犯
We've had some burglaries in the building.
-见到你很高兴  道格  -幸会
- It's nice to meet you, Doug. - Pleasure.
安德伍德夫人没告诉我你来这儿了
Mrs. Underwood didn't tell me you were in town.
我刚到  总统觉得我该来
I just got in. President thought it'd be a good idea
协助竞选事宜
if I were here to help coordinate on the campaign.
我还没正式加入呢
Well, I'm not officially on board yet.
我想看看明天会面的结果
I wanted to see how the meeting goes tomorrow.
会面
The meeting?
桃瑞丝·琼斯  第一夫人没告诉你吗
Doris Jones. The First Lady didn't tell you?
没有
No.
失陪一下
Will you excuse me for a moment?
-我去打个电话  -好的
- I just have to make a quick call. - Of course.
是总统
It's the president.
喂
Hello?
道格告诉我你对他举枪了
Doug tells me you greeted him with a firearm.
嗯  我们遇到了些问题...
Yeah, we've been having some issues with--
你知道枪哪点让我着迷吗  莉安
Do you know what fascinates me about guns, LeAnn?
扣下扳机  砰
You pull a trigger and bang,
一颗子弹喷出  快过声速
a bullet explodes out faster than the speed of sound.
如果你站的不是地方
And if you're on the wrong end of that bullet,
你还没听到声就会被它击中
why, it hits you before you even hear it.
总统先生  请原谅  但是
Mr. President, forgive me, but--
不  听着  莉安
No, I want you to hear me, LeAnn.
你要停下跟克莱尔的胡闹
You will walk away from this nonsense with Claire.
你不要打电话  也不要接电话
You will not make a phone call nor answer one.
不要解释
You will offer no explanation.
不管你跟我妻子谈了什么
Whatever you discussed with my wife,
你要全部忘记  永远不再提及
you will erase it from your mind and never speak of it again.
告诉我你听到了
Tell me I've been heard.
是的  我听到了
Yes, I heard you.
很好
Good.
真可爱
This is cute.
请把它放下
Put it down, please.
当纪念品了
Souvenir.
电话也给我吧
I'll take that phone, too.
今晚愉快
Have a good night.
多快
How soon?
法官正在审核减刑规则
The judge is reviewing the Rule 35 order now.
他一签字  他们逮捕了人
I mean, once he signs it, if they make an arrest,
这些人很快就能想明白
it won't take these guys long to figure out
是我跟联调局告密了
it was me that talked to the Feds.
他一签字  那就是几小时  而不是几天的事
Well, once he signs, it'll be a matter of hours, not days.
证人保护计划的安排已经定好了
The WITSEC arrangements are already being made.
-你知道他们要送我去哪吗  -不
- You know where they're sending me? - Nope.
我不会知道的  没人会知道
And I never will. Nobody will.
除了司法部
Except for the DOJ.
如果你有事要找我
If you need to reach me for anything,
你得通过证人保护计划负责人联系我
you're gonna have to contact me through the WITSEC officer.
我怕的不仅是亚美尼亚人
It's not just the Armenians I'm afraid of.
-卢卡斯  -我知道你一直不信
- Lucas... - I know you never believed me
-我说的总统的那些事  -听着  听好
- about the president but-- - Look. Listen carefully.
美国政府现在不是你的敌人了
The U.S. Government is not your enemy now.
好吗  他们在保护你
Okay? They're protecting you.
他就是政府
He is the government.
连白宫都不知道谁能靠减刑规则获释
Not even the White House knows who gets released on Rule 35.
除非司法部长说出去
Unless the Attorney General tells them,
几乎从来没有那种事
which almost never happens.
听着
Listen.
你干得很不错  卢卡斯
You did good work here, Lucas.
你要出去了
You're getting out.
开心点吧
Try to be happy about that.
你就这么放松吗
This how you unwind?
我从没来过这里
I've never been here in my life.
我想找个不会被认出来的地方
I wanted some place we wouldn't be recognized.
摆球吧
Rack 'em up.
-你说你有东西给我  -是的
- You said you had something to offer. - Yes.
保险
Insurance.
我们拿下了爱荷华州
We took Iowa.
在新罕布什尔州也追上来了
We're closing the gap in New Hampshire.
你们在爱荷华州是勉强通过
You squeaked by in Iowa.
周二之前你在新罕布什尔是追不上差距的
You're not gonna close the gap in New Hampshire by Tuesday.
-你自信过头了  -你还是新闻发言人呢
- You're overconfident. - And you're still Press Secretary.
他可没让你做幕僚长
He didn't make you Chief of Staff.
别告诉我你没想往那儿钻
Don't tell me you weren't angling for it.
你想要什么
What's your ask?
一件我们可用的事
One solid thing for us to work with.
如果打击了他  你就有个垫子了
It tanks him, you got a cushion.
如果没用
It doesn't?
你还能继续在白宫工作
You still have your job in the White House.
我凭什么信你
Why should I trust you?
如果你输了  不想有个后备计划吗
Wouldn't you rather have a back-up plan in your pocket if you lose?
该你了
Your shot.
我们保证给你在政府留个位置
We guarantee you a place in our administration
我做两年的幕僚长
after my two years as Chief of Staff.
然后就是你
Then it's you.
告诉我德州是怎么回事
Tell me what's happening in Texas.
-安德伍德夫人  -议员女士  见到你真高兴
- Mrs. Underwood. - Congresswoman, so good to see you.
我也很高兴  请进吧
Wonderful to see you, too. Please, come in.
西莉娅  见到你也很高兴
Celia, so good to see you, too.
很高兴  安德伍德夫人
Always a pleasure, Mrs. Underwood.
莉安早先给我打电话  说她来不了了
LeAnn called me a little while ago. Said she couldn't make it.
议员女士  我叫莉安安排这次会议
Congresswoman, I asked LeAnn to have this meeting set up
是因为我有个大胆的提议
because I have a radical proposal,
我想当面跟你提出
and I wanted to make it in person.
道格已经跟我说了
Well, Doug has already filled me in.
我一般不会为任何人背书四年
Usually, I wouldn't endorse anyone four years out,
但这次  我乐意考虑
but in this case, I'm really open to it.
能让民主党人进入州长府邸就好
Anything to put a Democrat into the governor's mansion.
我跟议员女士说
I told the congresswoman that
用上她在达拉斯的政治力量
enlisting her political machinery in Dallas
是很关键的第一步
is a crucial first step.
所以我叫我女儿也一起来了
Which is why I asked my daughter to join us.
到时她已经接替了我的席位  你俩可以密切合作
She'll have my seat by then, and you two will work closely.
我对您十分敬重  安德伍德夫人
I have a great deal of respect for you, Mrs. Underwood.
我认为我们携手可以成就辉煌
I think we can accomplish a lot together.
其实  议员女士
Well, actually, Congresswoman,
我认为如果不先当选公职
I've decided that the governorship is a big leap
直接做州长跨度太大
without holding any elected office first.
你在考虑下一轮竞选参议员吗
Are you thinking Senate next cycle?
不  我在考虑本轮竞选你的选区
No, I'm thinking your district, this cycle.
那样的话  您女儿就得等等
That would mean your daughter holds off,
等我竞选州长时
and then I would throw my full weight behind her
会全力支持她接替我
to replace me when I run for governor.
我已经组织了团队
I've already put together my team.
不  你还是能得到席位的  西莉娅
Oh, no, you would still get the seat, Celia.
我只是求你再等等
I'm just asking you to wait a little longer.
总统认为这个方案最好
And the president thinks this is the best plan.
你怎么没说
Why didn't you tell me this?
-我并不知道  夫人  -他和我私下谈的
- I wasn't aware, ma'am. - Well, he and I spoke privately about it.
西莉娅为了等我退休已经等了十年多
Celia has waited over a decade for me to retire.
该轮到她了
It's her time.
我理解
I understand.
所以等她接过了席位  我希望能给她
And that's why I want to put her in the best position to succeed
-最有利的地位  -你上次踏入
- when she takes office. - When was the last time
这个选区是什么时候了
you set foot in this district?
弗兰西斯当选党鞭的时候
When Francis was elected whip.
我们要怎么要求选民支持一个
So, how are we supposed to ask our people to support a woman
根本不了解他们的女人
that doesn't even know them?
不了解他们的生活  他们每日的挣扎
Their lives, their everyday struggles.
投机谋利
Carpetbagger.
还是白人
Who's white.
不仅是种族问题  安德伍德夫人
It goes deeper than race, Mrs. Underwood.
你在海兰帕克长大  从小不缺吃穿
You grew up in Highland Park, never wanted for anything.
你无法体现我们的群体
You just don't reflect our community.
议员女士说得有道理
Congresswoman makes a good point.
我是想要个跳板
What I want is a stepping stone.
而你想联邦资助一家计划生育组织经营的
And what you want is federal funding for a breast cancer center
乳腺癌中心
run by Planned Parenthood.
如果共和党控制了国会  这就无法实现
Something that a Republican-controlled Congress will never do.
尤其是在退伍军人医院
Especially in a VA hospital.
即便是民主党控制国会时你也遭遇了阻力
You had resistance even when the Democrats controlled the House.
但国会议员  不管是共和党还是民主党
But there's not one congressperson, Republican or Democrat,
都不会拒绝跟第一夫人见面
that would refuse a meeting with the First Lady.
你说得对  安德伍德夫人
You're right, Mrs. Underwood.
我们没能实现我们的一切目标
We haven't accomplished everything we set out to do.
但我的选民一直拥有的
But the one thing my constituents have always had...
是由自己人代表的骄傲
is the pride that they take in being represented by one of their own.
我不想剥夺这份骄傲
I refuse to rob them of that.
多谢您抽时间  议员女士
Thank you for your time, Congresswoman.
我们会重新考虑再联系您  谢谢
We'll reassess our thinking and get back to you. Thank you.
你叫总统别插手
You tell the president to stay out of this.
或许您该直接跟他谈
Maybe you should speak to him directly.
如果他肯支持我竞选  我就跟他谈
As soon as he's willing to support this race, I'll talk to him.
您在犯错误  安德伍德夫人
You're making a mistake, Mrs. Underwood.
白宫内部人士透露
A source within the White House tells us this,
第一夫人跟丈夫
that the First Lady traveled to Texas
大吵一架后飞去了德州
after some sort of a major argument with her husband.
第一夫人在德州  初选工作还是婚姻分歧
总统称她去达拉斯
Well, the president has claimed that she went to Dallas
是为德州初选打基础
to lay groundwork for the Texas primary.
但她三天前抵达后  却不见举办任何
But there's no evidence of any campaign events or fundraisers
竞选活动或筹款活动
since she arrived there three days ago,
也未曾公开露面
and she hasn't appeared publicly.
那么  莫妮卡  得问问你对此事的看法
So, Monica, gotta get your take on this.
如果真的出现了婚姻不和
Well, if there is marital discord,
安德伍德夫妇肯定不愿承认
the Underwoods certainly wouldn't want to admit it.
她去那边筹备初选
Her being down there for the primary?
拜托  那完全可能是障眼法
Come on, that could be a smokescreen.
-胡安  -格雷琴  我们现实点
- Juan? - Well, come on, Gretchen. Let's be real.
南卡罗莱纳州有蹊跷啊
Something's rotten in the state of Denmark.
这时机简直太糟了
I mean, the timing on this could not be worse.
别忘了  新罕布什尔初选就在明天
Don't forget, the New Hampshire primary is tomorrow.
总统从爱荷华州带出来的好势头
So, whatever momentum the president had coming out of Iowa...
现在都像气球泄气一样流逝了
Just like air going out of a popped balloon.
海瑟·邓巴对此
Well, you know that Heather Dunbar
肯定有话说  我们看看吧
is gonna have something to say about this. Let's take a look.
我不知道此事是真是假
I don't know whether this story is true or not,
海瑟·邓巴  针对安德伍德婚姻传言的回应
但如果是  我希望总统和第一夫人
but if it is, I hope that the president and the First Lady
能调和矛盾
can work out their differences.
没人希望看到一段婚姻出现问题
No one likes to see a marriage under strain.
个人而言  如果不是我了不起的家人
Personally, I wouldn't be able to carry on my campaign
我也没法竞选...
without the incredible...
知道是哪里走漏的消息吗
Do we know where the leak came from?
我们在找特勤局和员工问话
We're talking to Secret Service and to staff now,
但是  先生  暂时还不知道
but no, sir, we don't know yet.
我这儿有一堆十磅重的剪报
I'm looking at a ten-pound stack of clippings,
这还只是过去一小时里出来的报道
and that's just what's been written in the past hour.
这是邓巴干的  我知道是她捣的鬼
This is Dunbar. I know she's behind this.
先生  我可能有办法了
Sir, I might have a solution.
我们能单独谈谈吗
May we speak privately for a moment?
好  赛斯  挂线
Yeah. Seth, hop off the line.
如果我们要改变策略  我觉得...
If we're gonna switch tactics, I think I should--
如果总统打算采取措施我会告诉你的
I'll fill you in if the president wants to move forward.
挂线  赛斯
Hop off, Seth.
在辩论中  我们只记得
During the debates, we all remember,
安德伍德攻击夏普把孩子送去私立学校
Underwood went after Sharp for sending her kids to private...
好吧  说吧
All right, go ahead.
克莱尔的母亲
Claire's mother.
她怎么了
What about her?
第一夫妇吵架  克莱尔·安德伍德走人
你五岁的时候我就告诉你
I told you when you were five years old
进屋一定要跟我打招呼
not to come in this house without saying hello to me.
我到时就去看过你  你当时睡了
I came by when I arrived. You were asleep.
那是两天前了
That was two days ago.
我不知道你是不是想见我  母亲
Well, I wasn't sure you wanted to see me, Mother.
好吧
Well...
既然我们要生活在一个屋檐下
as long as we're living under the same roof
-而且还被新闻车包围  -那个很抱歉
- and besieged by news trucks-- - I apologize for all that.
是真的吗
Is it true?
你是因为这个才过来的吗
Is that why you came down here?
不  我来是因为
No, I came down here because...
那个来访的女人
That woman who visited...
-莉安·哈维  -我知道她是谁
- LeAnn Harvey. - Mmm-hmm, I know who she is.
她推销候选人的时候经常打给我
She calls me all the time asking for money when she's...
问我要钱
peddling some candidate.
你是候选人吗
Are you the candidate?
国会  30选区
Congress. 30th District.
这样啊
I see.
你不赞成
You don't approve.
你总是自己做决定
Well, you've always made your choices
不管我怎么想
regardless of what I think.
他怎么想
What does he think?
他跟你谈话了吗  劝我别那么做
Has he spoken to you? To discourage me?
你爸爸葬礼那天之后他就再没跟我说过话
He hasn't spoken to me since the day of your daddy's funeral.
你也一样
Just like you haven't.
你当上第一夫人都不来通电话
Not even a phone call when you became First Lady--
如果你不希望我待在这儿  我可以另做安排
If you don't want me here, I can make other arrangements.
别傻了
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
这房子是我的也是你的
This house is as much yours as it is mine.
我把东西都罩上
I put covers on everything
是因为女仆要清扫我从不进的房间
because the maids were cleaning rooms I never set foot in.
但既然你来了
But now that you're here...
别动了
Just leave them.
我只需要一间卧室
I only need a bedroom.
好吧
Fine.
这房子对你来说就是个旅馆
This house is just a hotel to you.
总统今天下午晚些时候会抵达达拉斯
The president will arrive in Dallas later this afternoon.
至于他此行的目的  我目前不能透露
As to the nature of his trip, I can't comment at this time
只能说他打算见第一夫人
other than to say he plans on seeing the First Lady.
-赛斯  -马克
- Seth! - Mark.
他南下似乎让他们出现婚姻问题的说法
His going down there would seem to lend legitimacy
看起来更有依据了  不是吗
to claims that they're having marital issues, wouldn't it?
我们已经否认了那种说法
We've already denied those claims.
-赛斯  -莎拉
- Seth! - Sara.
报道爆出后  总统
Neither the president nor the First Lady
和第一夫人都未曾公开做过回应
have publicly responded since this story broke.
他们会回应吗
Can we expect them to?
你所谓的报道  并非报道
What you're calling a story isn't a story.
只是个夺人眼球的标题
It's a flashy headline
帮你们在推特上涨粉
that gives you a bump in Twitter followers.
根本不值得对此做出回应
It doesn't warrant a response,
但如果总统或第一夫人决定回应
but if the president or First Lady chooses to make one,
肯定第一个告诉你
you'll be the first to know.
-赛斯  -谢谢大家
- Seth! - Thank you all very much.
-她离开多久了  -没多久
- How long has she been gone? - Not long.
-去了莉安·哈维办公室  -老天
- LeAnn Harvey's office. - Christ.
媒体没跟着她吧
The press didn't follow her, did they?
没有  他们走了条公用设施路
No. They took a utility road out.
没有警察随行
No police escort.
你俩要把问都不问一声就跑来
Are you two gonna make a habit of showing up here
当成习惯吗
without even the courtesy of asking?
我也希望不用来这儿
I wish I didn't have to be here,
但你女儿逼得我没办法
but your daughter's made it necessary.
她结婚时
You know, when she got married,
我以为过一两年她肯定会醒悟
I was sure she would wake up in a year or two.
没想到她用了30年
I had no idea it was gonna take her 30.
克莱尔是美国的第一夫人
Claire is the First Lady of the United States,
你还觉得她选错了人
and you still think she made the wrong choice.
变成小报谈资了
Reduced to tabloid gossip?
她跟住在你出身的那个拖车公园有什么区别
She might as well be living in that trailer park you come from.
是个桃子园
Well, it was a peach farm.
但你没说错  我还是白人垃圾
But you're right, I am still white trash.
我只不过恰好是个住在白宫的白人垃圾
I just happen to be white trash that lives in the White House.
就算当上总统  还是那么粗俗
Not even being president could give you any class.
我告诉你接下来会怎么样吧  伊丽莎白
Well, let me tell you what's about to happen, Elizabeth.
我不会站在交火的总统
I am not going to put myself in the crossfire
和第一夫人之间
between a president and First Lady.
我来应付弗兰西斯
Oh, I'll handle Francis.
你说他同意的
You said he was on board.
我会让他同意的
And I'll make sure he is.
重点是  你误导了我  安德伍德夫人
The point is you misled me, Mrs. Underwood.
你想要什么  莉安  钱吗
What is it you want, LeAnn? Is it money?
还是想要更多  留下真正的痕迹
Or do you want more, to make a real mark?
我不用选  我可以兼得
I don't have to choose. I can have both.
如果你想青史留名  你就得离开德州
Well, if you wanna make history, you need to get out of Texas.
我拒绝过不少华府的工作
I've turned down plenty of jobs in D.C.
一年应付15位客户
Juggling 15 clients a year.
但我想要你接下来15年的时间
But I want the next 15 years of your life.
德州只是我们的起点
Texas is just where we begin.
看来你到底是没听到
It seems you didn't hear me after all.
我不向威胁低头
I don't respond to threats.
你在跟总统说话
You're speaking to the president.
是的  我认得出他的声音
Yes, I recognize his voice.
请让我单独跟我妻子谈谈
I'd like to talk to my wife alone, please.
她留下  你想跟我说什么就说吧
She stays. Tell me what you need to tell me.
道格
Doug.
她已经病了三年了
She's been sick for three years.
放疗  化疗  都做了
Radiation, chemotherapy, the works.
但你不知道  是吗
But you didn't know, did you?
你不能把我母亲拉到镜头前
You're not dragging my mother in front of the cameras.
只有你一人  你要说你是为此才南下
Just you, and you're going to say that that's why you're down here.
这是家事  弗兰西斯
This is a family matter, Francis.
这事必须做  克莱尔  我们得把传言止住
This has to be done, Claire. We have to kill this story.
他说得对
He's right.
我要知道你不会给我的竞选捣乱
I need to know you won't meddle with my campaign.
国情咨文就在两周之后
The State of the Union is in two weeks.
你到时要来  我就不再阻挠你
You show up for that, then I'll leave you alone.
我们赶紧了事吧
Let's get this over with.
克莱尔最初来到达拉斯时
When Claire first came down here to Dallas...
我们说是为德州的初选打基础
we said it was to lay the groundwork for the Texas primary.
这也算是事实
And that was partially true.
但我们没说的  是一些本想保密的私事
What we left out was something that we hoped to keep private.
但鉴于这几天来关于我们婚姻状况的
But in light of false stories over the last number of days
漫天谣传
about the state of our marriage,
我们现在认为只能说出这一不幸的消息
we now feel it's important to share this unfortunate news.
克莱尔
Claire.
这三年来
For the past three years,
我母亲一直在与间歇性淋巴癌做抗争
my mother has been suffering from intermittent lymphoma.
起初  她在与病魔的抗争中取得了胜利
Initially, she had some success battling her illness,
但这几个月  疾病复发而且非常严重
but it's come back full force the last several months.
所以  我来这儿陪她
So, I came down here to spend time with her
进行进一步的治疗
while she undergoes further treatment.
看在我母亲尊严和健康的分上
And we ask just for the sake of my mother's dignity...
我们请求大家尊重她的隐私
and well-being that you respect her privacy.
谢谢
Thank you.
我明天将继续我的竞选
I will be resuming my campaign tomorrow
克莱尔  当然了  将留在这里
and Claire will, of course, be staying here.
我还要说
And let me just add...
克莱尔的母亲有这样孝顺的女儿是莫大的福气
Claire's mother is blessed to have such a loving daughter.
我有如此体贴  善良的妻子也是三生有幸
And I am blessed to have such a thoughtful and caring wife.
谢谢大家
Thank you all very much.
平平常常  但也足矣了
Nothing fancy, but it'll do the job.
你正式是约翰·卡莱尔了
You're officially John Carlyle now.
驾照有意弄了个过期的  你得乘大巴上班
Driver's license is expired on purpose. You take the bus to work.
把一切都背下来  地址  生日  社保号
Memorize everything, address, birthday, social.
还有个人经历  也要熟练背下来
There's a personal history in there for you to know by heart, too.
-"飞马租车行"  -对
- "Pegasus Car Rentals"? - Yeah.
你洗租车  明天开始
You wash rentals. It starts tomorrow.
保持低调
Keep a low profile.
别表现出异常
Don't be weird about it,
别到处交朋友
don't go out of your way to make friends.
如果...
What if there's...
出什么事了呢
If something's wrong?
固话直接接到我们本地办公室
Landline goes directly to our local office.
出门在外  用旁边那部手机
Away from home, use the cell phone next to it.
还有什么  你有基本的有线台
What else? You have basic cable.
没有网络  不用说
No Internet, obviously.
百叶窗拉好  门锁好
Keep the blinds drawn and the doors locked.
就这样了
That's it.
本周晚些时候我再来找你
I'll check in with you later this week.
我们不仅在新罕布什尔获胜
Now, we didn't just win a plurality here in New Hampshire.
而且差距悬殊
We won a majority.
知道这意味着什么吗
Now, you know what that tells me?
看来等票全数完  邓巴能领先
It's looking like Dunbar's got it by 11 or 12 points
11或12个百分点
by the time everything's counted.
已经报上来几个区了
How many precincts have reported?
两分钟前是83%
As of two minutes ago, 83%.
赛斯起草了讲话  等我们落地后用
Seth drafted a speech for when we land.
一般来说  邓巴会等你先发表讲话
Normally, Dunbar would wait to give her speech until after yours,
但既然我们在飞机上
but since we're on the plane--
-给她打电话  我让她  -好  先生
- Get her on the phone and I'll concede. - Yes, sir.
看那个乳臭未干的小白脸
Look at that snot-nosed pretty-boy.
他肯定刚学会刮胡子
I'll bet he just learned how to shave.
接邓巴
Get me Dunbar.
-女士  我真觉得...  -开门
- Ma'am, I really think-- - Open it.
她想一个人待着
She wants to be left alone.
打开门
Unlock the door.
你走
I want you to go!
母亲
Mother...
你为什么没告诉我
why didn't you tell me?
因为不关你的事
Because it was none of your business.
-听我说  -不  别费口舌了
- Just listen to me. - No, don't even bother.
我明白你为什么那么做
I understand why you did what you did.
但也还是一样伤人
But that doesn't make it any less hurtful.
那是为了我还是为了你自己
Is that for me or for yourself?
克莱尔
Claire.
过来
Come here.
你比他强大
You're stronger than he is.
但你得让他知道自己的位置
But you gotta put him in his place.